

TAHMID HASAN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Address

Ghudderdangi, Old Satkhira

Contact

web.tahmid@outlook.com

+88 01742 457673 **Twitter:** twitter.com/dev_tahmid

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/tahmid-hasan
Github: github.com/tahmid-hasan



ABOUT ME

A self-motivated technology expert with a focus on Full-Stack development desires to work with your Organization as a Web Developer to contribute to creating an extraordinary experience for the company's technical audience. Advanced knowledge of Object-Oriented JavaScript, Node, Vue, Angular, React, modern JS libraries, CSS, HTML5, TypeScript, and Python will be put to maximum use along with strong skills and ability in writing clean and efficient code.



WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

Web Developer, Jan 2015 - Now

I left DATAPARK BD LIMITED and started to work as a fulltime Freelancer in Web Development. In the meantime, I decided to learn NodeJS and Angular for turn my career to the full-stack development section. I've done a couple of projects in NodeJs. I like to challenge myself. I like to learn - so I like to try new things and try to keep growing.

DATAPARK BD LIMITED

System Engineer, Apr 2015 - Jan 2017

As a part of my IT career, I have joined Datapark (BD) Limited which is one of the brightest limited company in IT sector in Bangladesh. I'm working here as their system engineer. My objective for this position is to provide them with every kind of IT support, internal networking, maintain their local server and distribute the bandwidth between office stuff.

OUTSOURCING NET BD

Web Developer & Team Manager, Feb 2013 - Dec 2014

I started my basic IT career on Outsourcing NET BD. It's an IT farm based on outsourcing work. I'm working here as a web developer. My objective for this position is to provide the IT support and develop websites as their client's demand. I've also maintained their website and company database.



EDUCATION

SATKHIRA POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE

Satkhira, 20010-2015 Diploma in Electronics Result: On Processing

SATKHIRA GOVT HIGH SCHOOL

Satkhira, 2005-2010 Secondary School Certificate (Humanities) Result: GPA 4.56 in the scale of 5.00

FAST CARE TECHNOLOGY LIMITED

Panthapath, Dhaka, 2014-2015 CCNA (Pathway Course) Result: GPA 5.00 in the scale of 5.00



IT SKILLS

Node.js	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
Vue	•	•	•	O	•	•	•	•	0
Angular	•	()	O	O	•	•	•	•	\circ
React	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
HTML5	•	•	•	O	•	•	•	•	
CSS3	•	()	O	O	•	•	•	O	•
MongoDB	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Python	•	•	•	O	•	•	•	0	\circ
Adobe Illustrator	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Adobe Photoshop	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0



PERSONAL SKILLS

Social Commitment	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Organization	()	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
Creativity	()	O	•	•	•	()	O	O	0
Communication	•	()	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
Teamwork	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0



LANGUAGES

Bengali	()	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	
English	()	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	
Hindi	•	•		•	\circ	0	\circ	\circ	0	



AWARDS

SHILPAKALA ACADEMY ART COMPITITION AWARD

Satkhira, Bangladesh, 2005

This competition organized by Shilpakala Academy Satkhira. It was organized for 21th February The International Mother Language day. I took part in this competition and achieved 3rd place between 143 competitors. And got awarded.

NATIONAL SIENCE ACADEMY QUIZE CONTEST 2012 Satkhira, Bangladesh, 2012

This is a quiz competition organized by Bangladesh science academy. I took part in this competition and have gained the 1st place between 65 competitors.



HOBBIES AND ACTIVITIES



Bicycle riding



Badminton



Photography



Travelling



Signing



Coding

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Tahmid Hasan

Father's Name: MD. Ruhul Amin

Mother's Name: MST. Shahnawaz Parvin

Date of Birth: May 3, 1993

Sex: Male

Address (Present): Flat 3B, House #32 (Nur Mahal), Road #14, Rupnager R/A

Section -2, Mirpur, Dhaka, 1216

Address (Permanent): Ghudderdangi, Old Satkhira

Satkhira, 9400

Nationality: Bangladeshi

Religion: Islam

Marital Status: Unmarried